<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
        <title>BrushBuddy Blog</title>
        <description>BrushBuddy Blog - Daniel Medeiros</description>
        <link>https://blog.brushbuddy.net</link>
        <atom:link href="https://blog.brushbuddy.net/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 21:34:59 -0600</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 21:34:59 -0600</pubDate>
        <ttl>60</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Brushbuddy website is live!</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Website is finally up! At least up enough to start using!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://blog.brushbuddy.net/2020/11/02/2020-Website/</link>
                <guid>https://blog.brushbuddy.net/2020/11/02/2020-Website</guid>
                <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 14:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Oral Health</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you know what the most prevalent chronic disease in both children and adults in the United States is?
As you may have guessed, that is dental caries (tooth decay).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NIH (National Institutes of Health) maintains statistics of tooth decay, and the data is shocking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you do not clean your teeth regularly, plaque can being to build up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plaque is a colorless, sticky film that covers the surfaces of your teeth. It’s primarily made up of bacteria, food particles and salive.
Over time, plaque will start to harden, forming something called tartar
Tartar can start to form in a matter of hours, which is why its important to brush. The American Dental Association (ADA) recommends brushing at least twice per day, two minutes at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tartar and plaque can cause bad breath, destroy enamel (the outer layer of your teeth), and promote gum disease).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the enamel is weakened, small holes in your teeth called cavities, or dental caries can form. The only way to treat cavities is to have them filled by your dentist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next step is dentin decay. Dentin is the tissue under the enamel. It is softer, which makes it more susceptible to damage. 
Dentin contains tubes that lead to the nerves, which may cause sensitivity to hot or cold drinks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decay will then reach the pulp, which is the innermost layer of your tooth. It contains the nerves and blood vessels that keep the tooth healthy.
When damage to the pulp occurs, you will start to feel pain. The treatment at this stage is often a root canal.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://blog.brushbuddy.net/2020/11/02/Oral-Health/</link>
                <guid>https://blog.brushbuddy.net/2020/11/02/Oral-Health</guid>
                <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 14:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Welcome to the Brushbuddy Blog!</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog will detail the journey to get Brushbuddy to market. This will be a revolutionary product to help people everywhere to maintain good oral health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I welcome &lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt; on our journey, from prototype creation, vendor selection and updates during the development of this great product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>https://blog.brushbuddy.net/2020/11/01/first-post/</link>
                <guid>https://blog.brushbuddy.net/2020/11/01/first-post</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 14:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
